

## **BRAHMA** PUTRA

Software Engineer, Front-End

📞 +62 858 6226 6465 🏻 🛎 brahmaputra1996@gmail.com

## BRIEF INTRODUCTION

2017

A Software engineer with 4 years of experience, specialized in Front-End Web Development. Experienced in applying modern front-end framework (Vue/Nuxt). Proficient with the Jamstack development. Able to work in a fast-paced and highly collaborative work environment.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2018 - 2021 Software Engineer, Front-End

Cityplan.id | PT. Kolaborasi Ruang Indonesia

Web Developer [Intern]

Geologi | Ministry of Energy and Mineral Resource (ESDM)

2015-2016 Web Developer

25 Senior High School

20)5-2020 Freelance Visual Designer & Front-End Development

Freelancer.com

EDUCATION Bachelor of Computer Science (S. Kom)

Universitas Pendidikan Indonesia | 2013-2017

COMPETITION • 3rd Place Winner

IBM Watson AutoAl Data Challange 2021

PUBLICATION Data-to-text for generating information of weather and air

quality in the R programming language

Journal of Engineering Science and Technology
Vol. 14, No 1, 498-508, School of Engineering, Taylor University

SECIALIZATION Front-End Web Development

Javascript Frameworks & Libraries: Vue/Nuxt

CSS Preprocessor & UI Framework: SASS & MD with Vuetify

Version Control System : Git (GitHub, Bitbucket)

Prototyping: Figma

Graphic Editing & Production: Adobe Photoshop & Illustrator